<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Doug Logston's Life</title>
    <description>These are stories from Doug Logston's life.
</description>
    <link>http://douglogston.life/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://douglogston.life/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 00:46:55 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 00:46:55 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Laurie Bulkley</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I was thinking of Doug over the last couple of days and realized how
little I knew him... the famously picky eater, &amp;quot;But what IS it?&amp;quot; and
the cleaning obsession (vacuuming in the middle of a Christmas party
was a new one to me) but he was consistent about one thing - he always
lit up when Paul or Christopher entered the room. He loved his boys,
he really LOVED his boys and it showed on his face. How lucky you both
were to have that in your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;love,
Laurie&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 07:23:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://douglogston.life/laurie</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://douglogston.life/laurie</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Glenda Ballengee</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I've known your dad for a number of years even before your mom and dad
where married. What I didn't know about him was he need to clean. When
my son Ricky was about 10 he used to stop at your Condo on the way back
from school, when I picked him up I stayed a bit and talked to your mom
until your dad came home. When he came in he immediately started to organize
and clean the house, out came the vacuum cleaner and all the toys you guys were
playing with had to be picked up and put away even if you were in the middle
of playing everything had to be put away and he started vacuuming, once he
stopped with the vacuum he started in on the kitchen even if Eileen had just
cleaned it before he came home, I was dumbfounded on how he could work all day
and then come home and do this, I asked Eileen if he was OCD she said yep and
it was his way of winding down from the day, I thought if he needed more
unwinding he could come to my place and un-wind a little more I had loads of
therapy for him at my house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other thing was how he loved and supported his boy's he loved to watch
them in their numerous roles and always had an encouraging word for them after
their performances in whatever play they were in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was a kind and generous man that loved his entire family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glenda&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 07:23:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://douglogston.life/glenda</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://douglogston.life/glenda</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Natalie Ashodian</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my most vivid memories of your dad (probably because it happened over an
over) were the 1-2, 1-2s! we'd beg him to do. Toss us in the pool over his head
at the old condo community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I had two pairs of his old work jeans, they took me through high school
and college. The best naturally &amp;quot;distressed&amp;quot; jeans a girl could ask for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think my mom still has some of his black jeans from later that she made bags
out of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also told me not to eat to many bananas or I'd &amp;quot;get the runs&amp;quot; and not to
&amp;quot;carry so much money in your wallet or you might lose it&amp;quot; ...I hoarded my good
report card money and carried it around around in my little kid wallet 'cause
i thought it made me mature. It did not. It made me an oddly cash rich kid.
#UncleDougAdvice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Natalie Ashodian&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 07:23:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://douglogston.life/natalie</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://douglogston.life/natalie</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beth Lenz</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Although my interactions with Mr. Logston were short, I remember he was always
very hospitable. When I visited Paul, his son, at their house in Hercules,
Mr. Logston would be sitting in his recliner watching the tv near the kitchen.
Usually, he would offer me a seat to join in on the fun. If I was in the kitchen
sitting at the island, he would get up and talk to me, offer me juice, water,
milk, a snack, even an entire meal. When Paul and I would get ready to go,
Mr. Logston would walk us out to say good-bye to Paul, chat for a little bit,
and checked in on the cats that Paul threw off the car as he walked back into
the house. He was a very loving father and made sure his sons' friends always
felt welcome under their roof, which was always the case for me.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 07:23:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://douglogston.life/elizabeth-lenz</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://douglogston.life/elizabeth-lenz</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
