<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Doug Logston's Life</title>
    <description>These are stories from Doug Logston's life.
</description>
    <link>http://douglogston.life/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://douglogston.life/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 19:21:42 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 19:21:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Natalie Ashodian</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my most vivid memories of your dad (probably because it happened over an
over) were the 1-2, 1-2s! we'd beg him to do. Toss us in the pool over his head
at the old condo community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I had two pairs of his old work jeans, they took me through high school
and college. The best naturally &amp;quot;distressed&amp;quot; jeans a girl could ask for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think my mom still has some of his black jeans from later that she made bags
out of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also told me not to eat to many bananas or I'd &amp;quot;get the runs&amp;quot; and not to
&amp;quot;carry so much money in your wallet or you might lose it&amp;quot; ...I hoarded my good
report card money and carried it around around in my little kid wallet 'cause
i thought it made me mature. It did not. It made me an oddly cash rich kid.
#UncleDougAdvice.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 04:23:06 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://douglogston.life/2015/03/28/natalie.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://douglogston.life/2015/03/28/natalie.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beth Lenz</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Although my interactions with Mr. Logston were short, I remember he was always
very hospitable. When I visited Paul, his son, at their house in Hercules,
Mr. Logston would be sitting in his recliner watching the tv near the kitchen.
Usually, he would offer me a seat to join in on the fun. If I was in the kitchen
sitting at the island, he would get up and talk to me, offer me juice, water,
milk, a snack, even an entire meal. When Paul and I would get ready to go,
Mr. Logston would walk us out to say good-bye to Paul, chat for a little bit,
and checked in on the cats that Paul threw off the car as he walked back into
the house. He was a very loving father and made sure his sons' friends always
felt welcome under their roof, which was always the case for me.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 04:23:06 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://douglogston.life/2015/03/28/elizabeth-lenz.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://douglogston.life/2015/03/28/elizabeth-lenz.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
